Rose Gerlach Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Wilson, Jim (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Bowery gallery, 1973 (Box 8)
- Wilson, May, b. 1905 (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Gimpel gallery, 1971 (Box 8)
- Wilson, York (4 slides) (Box 8)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1968 (Box 8)
- Windust (7 slides) (Box 8)
  - Westerly gallery, 1966 (Box 8)
- Wingate, Arline, b. 1906 (9 slides) (Box 8)
  - Funt gallery, 1966 (Box 8)
- Winsor, Jacqueline, b. 1941 (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Paula Cooper gallery, 1973 (Box 8)
- Wisseman (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Bodley gallery, 1969 (Box 8)
- Wisseman-Widrig, Nancy (3 slides) (Box 8)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery (Box 8)
- Witkin, Isaac, 1936-2006 (5 slides) (Box 8)
  - Elkon gallery, 1966 (Box 8)
- Wofford, Philip, b. 1936 (8 slides) (Box 8)
  - Stone gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
  - Bykert gallery, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Andre Emmerich gallery, 1972 (Box 8)
- Wohl (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Bodley gallery, 1969 (Box 8)
- Wojcik, Gary Thomas, b. 1945 (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1970 (Box 8)
- Wolfe, James, b. 1944 (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Andre Emmerich gallery, 1973 (Box 8)
- Wonner, Paul, b. 1920 (3 slides) (Box 8)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1971 (Box 8)
- Woodburn (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971 (Box 8)
- Woodham, Jean, b. 1925 (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Feigen gallery, 1966 (Box 8)
- Woodman (7 slides) (Box 8)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1968, 1970 (Box 8)
- Woodner, Ian, 1903-1990 (4 slides) (Box 8)
  - Weintraub gallery, 1969 (Box 8)
- Wright (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1966 (Box 8)
- Yacoe, Donald, 1923- (5 slides) (Box 8)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1968 (Box 8)
- Yamasaki, Minoru, 1912-1986 (4 slides) (Box 8)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1967 (Box 8)
- Yankowitz, Nina, b. 1946 (5 slides) (Box 8)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1969, 1971 (Box 8)
- Yokomi, Richard, b. 1944 (4 slides) (Box 8)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1971 (Box 8)
- Young, Peter Ford, b. 1940 (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Castelli gallery, 1968 (Box 8)
- Youngerman, Jack, b. 1926 (13 slides) (Box 8)
  - Byron gallery, 1965 (Box 8)
  - Pace gallery, 1971, 1972 (Box 8)
- Yrisarry, Mario, b. 1933 (also spelled Yrissary, Yrisary) (13 slides) (Box 8)
  - Graham gallery, 1965, 1967 (Box 8)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1971 (Box 8)
- Yvaral (Vasarely, Jean-Pierre), 1934-2002 (24 slides) (Box 8)
  - Contemporaries gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
  - FDU gallery, 1965 (Box 8)
  - Wise gallery, 1966 (Box 8)
- Zakanitch, Robert, b. 1935 (also spelled Zakanych) (7 slides) [Slide box 47] (Box 8)
  - Stable gallery, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Reese-Palley gallery, 1970, 1971 (Box 8)
- Zapkus, Keytutis, b. 1938 (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Paula Cooper gallery, 1973 (Box 8)
- Zobel (11 slides) (Box 8)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1965, 1968 (Box 8)
- Zogbaum, Wilfrid, 1915-1965 (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Borgenicht gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
- Zona (15 slides) (Box 8)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1966, 1968 (Box 8)
- Zox, Larry, 1937-2006 (16 slides) (Box 8)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1966, 1968, 1969, 1970, 1971 (Box 8)
  - Andre Emmerich gallery, 1973 (Box 8)
- Zucker, Joe, b. 1941 (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Reese-Palley gallery, 1972 (Box 8)
- Zvi (7 slides) (Box 8)
  - Bodley gallery, 1967 (Box 8)